NIGHTCLUBBING Archive by Pat Ivers and Emily Armstrong 1970-2009 (Bulk 1975-1980) MSS.305
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Performances
  - Raybeats at Danceteria, June 1980; ID: 305.0094 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0094, Box 30, Dvd 305.0094_a)
  - Suburbs at Danceteria, June 1980; ID: 305.0128 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0128, Box 31, Dvd 305.0128_a)
  - Suburbs at Danceteria, June 1980; ID: 305.0129 (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0129, Box 31, Dvd 305.0129_a)
    Duration: 49 minutes
  - Ballistic Kisses at Danceteria, July 1980; ID: 305.0108 (Box 6, Media ID: 305.0108, Box 30, Dvd 305.0108_a)
    Duration: 41 minutes
  - Buzz and the Flyers at Danceteria, July 1980; ID: 305.0110 (Box 6, Media ID: 305.0110, Box 30, Dvd 305.0110_a)
    Duration: 37 minutes
  - DNA at Danceteria, July 1980; ID: 305.0131 (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0131, Box 31, Dvd 305.0131_a)
    Duration: 27 minutes
  - Feelies at Danceteria, July 1980; ID: 305.0102 (Box 6, Media ID: 305.0102, Box 30, Dvd 305.0102_a)
  - Human Sexual Response at Danceteria, July 1980; ID: 305.0091 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0091, Box 30, Dvd 305.0091_a)
  - Kid Creole & the Coconuts at Danceteria, July 1980; ID: 305.0114 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0114, Box 30, Dvd 305.0114_a)
  - Outsets at Danceteria, July 1980; ID: 305.0103 (Box 6, Media ID: 305.0103, Box 30, Dvd 305.0103_a)
    Duration: 52 minutes
  - Suicide at Danceteria, July 1980; ID: 305.0112 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0112, Box 30, Dvd 305.0112_a)
  - Suicide at Danceteria, July 1980; ID: 305.0100 (Box 6, Media ID: 305.0100, Box 30, Dvd 305.0100_a)
    Duration: 36 minutes
  - Sun Ra at Danceteria, July 1980; ID: 305.0104 (Box 6, Media ID: 305.0104, Box 30, Dvd 305.0104_a)
  - Bush Tetras at Danceteria, August 1980; ID: 305.0122 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0122, Box 31, Dvd 305.0122_a)
  - Pylon at Danceteria, August 1980; ID: 305.0097 (Box 6, Media ID: 305.0097, Box 30, Dvd 305.0097_a)
    Duration: 43 minutes
  - Strange Party at Danceteria, August 1980; ID: 305.0096 (Box 6, Media ID: 305.0096, Box 30, Dvd 305.0096_a)
  - Ballistic Kisses at Danceteria, September 1980; ID: 305.0099 (Box 6, Media ID: 305.0099, Box 30, Dvd 305.0099_a)
  - Joe King Carrasco at Danceteria, September 1980; ID: 305.0111 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0111, Box 30, Dvd 305.0111_a)
    Alternate title: Joe King Carrasco at Danceteria, September 1980 2/2
  - Joe King Carrasco at Danceteria, September 1980; ID: 305.0072 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0072, Box 29, Dvd 305.0072_a)
    Duration: 00:31:23
  - Offs at Danceteria, September 1980; ID: 305.0124 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0124, Box 31, Dvd 305.0124_a)
    Alternate title: Offs at Danceteria, September 1980 1/2
  - Offs at Danceteria, September 1980; ID: 305.0113 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0113, Box 30, Dvd 305.0113_a)
    Alternate title: Offs at Danceteria, September 1980 2/2
  - Plastics at Danceteria, September 1980; ID: 305.0109 (Box 6, Media ID: 305.0109, Box 30, Dvd 305.0109_a)
  - Pylon at Danceteria, September 1980; ID: 305.0098 (Box 6, Media ID: 305.0098, Box 30, Dvd 305.0098_a)
  - Raybeats at Danceteria, September 1980; ID: 305.0095 (Box 6, Media ID: 305.0095, Box 30, Dvd 305.0095_a)
  - Revelons at Danceteria, September 1980; ID: 305.0115 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0115, Box 30, Dvd 305.0115_a)
    Alternate title: Revelons at Danceteria, September 1980 1/2
  - Revelons, Max Blagg at Danceteria, September 1980; ID: 305.0116 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0116, Box 30, Dvd 305.0116_a)
    Alternate title: Revelons, Max Blagg at Danceteria, September 1980 2/2
  - Snow Storm at Lower East Side, 1977; ID: 305.0144 (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0144, Box 31, Dvd 305.0144_a)
  - Rocket from the Tomb at Knitting Factory, June 2003; ID: 305.0118 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0118, Box 30, Dvd 305.0118_a)
    Original format: Betacam
  - Rocket from the Tomb at Knitting Factory, June 2003; ID: 305.0117 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0117, Box 30, Dvd 305.0117_a)
  - Bicentennial Time Capsules at Philadelphia, undated; ID: 305.0143 (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0143)
    Currently unavailable until duplication occurs.
    Tape too phyically deteriorated to preserve.
  - Erasers at CBGB, undated; ID: 305.0137 (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0137, Box 31, Dvd 305.0137_a)
    Alternate Title: Erasers at CBGB 1/3
  - Erasers at CBGB, undated; ID: 305.0138 (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0138, Box 31, Dvd 305.0138_a)
    Alternate Title: Erasers at CBGB 2/3
  - Erasers at CBGB, undated; ID: 305.0139 (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0139, Box 31, Dvd 305.0139_a)
    Alternate Title: Erasers at CBGB 3/3
  - Erasers Edit at CBGB, undated; ID: 305.0140 (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0140, Box 31, Dvd 305.0140_a)
  - The Greying [Greening] of Central Park at Central Park, undated; ID: 305.0145 (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0145, Box 31, Dvd 305.0145_a)
  - "Hell in Paradise": Contortions & Stimulators at Paradise Garage, undated; ID: 305.0135 (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0135, Box 31, Dvd 305.0135_a)
    Audio intermittant and distorted throughout; no audio from 18 minutes 30 seconds to 24 minutes.
  - "Hell in Paradise": Richard Hell at Paradise Garage, undated; ID: 305.0132 (Box 10, Media ID: 305.0132, Box 31, Dvd 305.0132_a)
  - "Hell in Paradise": Richard Hell at Paradise Garage, undated; ID: 305.0133 (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0133, Box 31, Dvd 305.0133_a)
    Duration: 28 minutes
  - "Hell in Paradise": Senders at Paradise Garage, undated; ID: 305.0136 (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0136, Box 31, Dvd 305.0136_a)
  - "Hell in Paradise": Teenage Jesus and the Jerks at Paradise Garage, undated; ID: 305.0134 (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0134, Box 31, Dvd 305.0134_a)
    Duration: 9 minutes
    Audio intermittant and distorted throughout.
  - Son at CBGB, undated; ID: 305.0142 (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0142, Box 31, Dvd 305.0142_a)
  - Startoons at CBGB, undated; ID: 305.0141 (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0141, Box 31, Dvd 305.0141_a)
  - Three Nights on a Revolving Stage, undated; ID: 305.0147 (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0147, Box 31, Dvd 305.0147_a)
  - Bicentennial Time Capsules at Philadelphia, undated; ID: 305.0151 (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0151, Box 31, Dvd 305.0151_a)
  - Bicentennial Time Capsules at Philadelphia, undated; ID: 305.0152 (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0152, Box 31, Dvd 305.0152_a)
  - Bicentennial Time Campsules at Philadelphia, undated; ID: 305.0153 (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0153, Box 31, Dvd 305.0153_a)
    Original fDVD access copy available.ormat: 1/2" open reel
  - Bicentennial Time Capsules at Philadelphia, undated; ID: 305.0150 (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0150, Box 31, Dvd 305.0150_a)
  - [Blank Tape], undated; ID: 305.0149 (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0149)
  - Womanland with Millionairs Overnight at ETC Studios, undated; ID: 305.0148 (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0148, Box 31, Dvd 305.0148_a)
- Series II: Interviews
  Series II contains video interviews with various musicians, performance artists, critics, and writers involved in the New York City punk scene. Many of the videos are undated. The dated interviews were all made in the 2000s except for one recording from 1977.
  - Joey Arias at Theater, March 10, undated; ID: 305.0181 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0181, Box 32, Dvd 305.0181_a)
    Original format: Betacam SX
    Alternate Title: Joey Arias at Theater, March 23
  - James Chance - Tape 1, undated; ID: 305.0179 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0179, Box 32, Dvd 305.0179_a)
    Alternate Title: James Chance at CBGB - Tape 1 of 2
  - James Chance - Tape 2, undated; ID: 305.0180 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0180, Box 32, Dvd 305.0180_a)
    Alternate Title: James Chance at CBGB - Tape 2 of 2
  - Cheeta Chrome at LA, June 9 [Year Unknown], ID: 305.0197 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0197, Box 32, Dvd 305.0197)
    Original format: Mini DV
  - Jay Dee Daugherty at CBGB, June 9 [Year Unknown], ID: 305.0209 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0209, Box 33, Dvd 305.0209)
    Duration: 42 minutes
  - Richard Hell - Tape 1, March 24, 2007; ID: 305.0170 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0170, Box 32, Dvd 305.0170_a)
    Alternate Title: Richard Hell at Winship's; March 24, 2007 - Tape 1 of 2
  - Richard Hell - Tape 2, March 25, 2007; ID: 305.0171 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0171, Box 32, Dvd 305.0171_a)
    Alternate Title: Richard Hell at Winship's; March 25, 2007 - Tape 2 of 2
  - Hilly & Cosmo at CBGB, May 9, 1977; ID: 305.0212 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0212, Box 33, Dvd 305.0212_a)
    Black & White, Color, Sound
  - Hilly Interview, undated; ID: 305.0176 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0176, Box 32, Dvd 305.0176_a)
    Alternate Title: [Hilly Krystal at CBGBs, March 2]
  - John Holstrom at Orchard Street (Year Unknown), May 1; ID: 305.0193 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0193, Box 32, Dvd 305.0193)
  - John Holstrom 2 at Orchard Street (Year Unknown), May 11; ID: 305.0194 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0194, Box 32, Dvd 305.0194)
  - Ivan Julian at Ivan's Studio, (Year Unknown), June 9; ID: 305.0198 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0198, Box 32, Dvd 305.0198)
  - Ivan Julian & Marcia Resnick at Ivan's Studio and Marcia's Apartment, (Year Unknown), June 9; ID: 305.0199 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0199, Box 32, Dvd 305.0199)
  - Lenny Kaye at Brooklyn Home, February 20, 2004; ID: 305.0182 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0182, Box 32, Dvd 305.0182_a)
    Alternate Title: Lenny Kaye at Brooklyn Home, February 20, 2004 1/2
  - Lenny Kaye at Brooklyn Home, February 20, 2004; ID: 305.0183 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0183, Box 32, Dvd 305.0183_a)
  - Stephanie Kaye - Tape 1, undated; ID: 305.0177 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0177, Box 32, Dvd 305.0177_a)
    Alternate Title: Stephanie Kaye at Bowery Loft; February 9 - Tape 1 of 2
  - Stephanie Kaye - Tape 2, undated; ID: 305.0178 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0178, Box 32, Dvd 305.0178_a)
    Alternate Title: Stephanie Kaye at Bowery Loft; February 9 - Tape 2 of 2
  - Arto Lindsay at Orchard Street, March 23 2002; ID: 305.0188 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0188, Box 32, Dvd 305.0188_a)
    Alternate Title: Arto Lindsay at Orchard Street, March 23 2002 1/2
  - Arto Lindsay at Orchard Street, March 23 2002; ID: 305.0189 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0189, Box 32, Dvd 305.0189_a)
    Item is currently unavailable.
    Alternate Title: Arto Lindsay at Orchard Street, March 23 2002 2/2
  - Richard Lloyd - Tape 1, May 11, 2002; ID: 305.0174 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0174, Box 32, Dvd 305.0174_a)
    Alternate Title: Richard Lloyd at His Studio; May 10, 2002 - Tape 1 of 2
  - Richard Lloyd - Tape 2, April 10, 2002; ID: 305.0175 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0175, Box 32, Dvd 305.0175_a)
    Alternate Title: Richard Lloyd at His Studio, April 10, 2002 - Tape 2 of 2
  - Lydia Lunch 1 at Orchard Street (Year Unknown), June 9; ID: 305.0207 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0207, Box 33, Dvd 305.0207)
  - Lydia Lunch 2 at Orchard Street (Year Unknown), June 9; ID: 305.0208 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0208, Box 33, Dvd 305.0208)
  - Walter Lure at Bayside Home (Year Unknown), May 2; ID: 305.0184 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0184, Box 32, Dvd 305.0184_a)
    Alternate Title: Walter Lure at Bayside Home, May 2 [Year Unknown] 1/2
  - Walter Lure at Bayside Home (Year Unknown), May 11; ID: 305.0185 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0185, Box 32, Dvd 305.0185_a)
    Alternate Title: Walter Lure at Bayside Home, May 11 [Year Unknown] 2/2
  - Pat Place at Pat's Loft (Year Unknown), June 9; ID: 305.0201 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0201, Box 33, Dvd 305.0201)
  - Mark Ramone 1 at Orchard Street (Year Unknown), June 9; ID: 305.0205 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0205, Box 33, Dvd 305.0205)
  - Mark Ramone 2 at Orchard Street (Year Unknown), June 9; ID: 305.0206 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0206, Box 33, Dvd 305.0206)
  - Marcia Resnick 2 at Marcia's Apartment (Year Unknown), June 9; ID: 305.0200 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0200, Box 33, Dvd 305.0200)
  - Michael Shore - Tape 1, undated; ID: 305.0172 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0172, Box 32, Dvd 305.0172_a)
    Duration: 30 minute
    Alternate Title: Michael Shore at MTV - Tape 1 of 2
  - Michael Shore - Tape 2, undated; ID: 305.0173 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0173, Box 32, Dvd 305.0173_a)
    Alternate Title: Michael Shore at MTV - Tape 2 of 2
  - Cynthia Sley at Pat's Loft (Year Unknown), June 9; ID: 305.0202 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0202, Box 33, Dvd 305.0202)
    Original format: Format: Mini DV
  - David Thomas 1 at LA (Year Unknown), June 9; ID: 305.0196 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0196, Box 32, Dvd 305.0196)
  - David Thomas 2 and Cheeta Chrome 1 at LA (Year Unknown), June 9; ID: 305.0195 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0195, Box 32, Dvd 305.0195)
  - Tish and Snooky, undated; ID: 305.0190 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0190, Box 32, Dvd 305.0190_a)
  - Tish & Snooky 1 at Manic Panic (Year Unknown), May 11; ID: 305.0191 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0191, Box 32, Dvd 305.0191)
  - Tish & Snooky 2 and Scratchy at Manic Panic and Orchard Street (Year Unknown), May 11; ID: 305.0192 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0192, Box 32, Dvd 305.0192)
  - Roy Trakin 1 at LA (Year Unknown), June 9; ID: 305.0203 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0203, Box 33, Dvd 305.0203)
  - Roy Trakin 2 at LA (Year Unknown), June 9; ID: 305.0204 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0204, Box 33, Dvd 305.0204)
  - Alan Vega at Orchard Street, March 2, 2002; ID: 305.0186 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0186, Box 32, Dvd 305.0186_a)
    Alternate Title: Alan Vega at Orchard Street, March 11 [Year Unknown] 1/2
  - Alan Vega at Orchard Street (Year Unknown), March 11; ID: 305.0187 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0187, Box 32, Dvd 305.0187_a)
    Alternate Title: Alan Vega at Orchard Street, March 11 [Year Unknown] 2/2
  - Jeff Magnum, undated; ID: 305.0210 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0210, Box 33, Dvd 305.0210)
  - Arto/Suicide, undated; ID: 305.0211 (Box 11, Media ID: 305.0211)
- Series III: The Come-On's
  The seven videos in Series III comprise two shoots and rough edits of The Come-On's video installation project. The project allowed participants to select to view a tape of a performer, or "seducer," in a photo booth. Each tape featured a musician or artist from the downtown scene who attempted to "seduce" the viewer.
  - The Come-On's: Shoot 1, #1, undated; ID: 305.0213 (Box 12, Media ID: 305.0213, Box 33, Dvd 305.0213_a)
  - The Come-On's: Shoot 1, #2, undated; ID: 305.0214 (Box 12, Media ID: 305.0214, Box 33, Dvd 305.0214_a)
  - The Come-On's: Shoot 1, #3, undated; ID: 305.0215 (Box 12, Media ID: 305.0215, Box 33, Dvd 305.0215_a)
  - The Come-On's: Shoot 2, #1, undated; ID: 305.0216 (Box 12, Media ID: 305.0216, Box 33, Dvd 305.0216_a)
  - The Come-On's: Shoot 2, #2, undated; ID: 305.0217 (Box 12, Media ID: 305.0217, Box 33, Dvd 305.0217_a)
  - The Come-On's: Rough Edit, undated; ID: 305.0218 (Box 12, Media ID: 305.0218, Box 33, Dvd 305.0218_a)
  - The Come-On's: Rough Edit, undated; ID: 305.0219 (Box 12, Media ID: 305.0219, Box 33, Dvd 305.0219_a)
- Series IV: Narrative Tapes
  The six videos in Series IV comprise narrative tapes, which functioned as the precursor to modern music videos. In each narrative tape, an artist's performance is accompanied by thematically relevant stories, images, and video clips.
  - European Ashes, 1982; ID: 305.0223 (Box 12, Media ID: 305.0223, Box 33, Dvd 305.0223_a)
    Duration: 6 minutes
  - European Ashes, undated; ID: 305.0224 (Box 10, Media ID: 305.0224, Box 33, Dvd 305.0224_a)
  - Boy's Backs, undated; ID: 305.0221 (Box 12, Media ID: 305.0221, Box 33, Dvd 305.0221_a)
    Duration: 4 minutes
  - Chain of Fools, Boy's Backs, undated; ID: 305.0220 (Box 12, Media ID: 305.0220, Box 33, Dvd 305.0220_a)
    Duration: 51 minutes
  - Samurai Toys, undated; ID: 305.0225 (Box 12, Media ID: 305.0225, Box 33, Dvd 305.0225_a)
  - Surfclubbing, Rockabilly Romance, undated; ID: 305.0222 (Box 12, Media ID: 305.0222, Box 33, Dvd 305.0222_a)
- Series V: Video Lounge
  The nineteen videos in Series V contain Video Lounge footage captured by Ivers and Armstrong. The artists created the Video Lounge format after being commissioned to design a video installation for the opening of the Danceteria nightclub in 1980. Video Lounge became a permanent feature at Danceteria but Ivers and Armstrong also included the format in the NIGHTCLUBBING television series, which showed video art, various video clips and footage, and musical performances.
  - Betty Boop Cartoons, undated; ID: 305.0226 (Box 12, Media ID: 305.0226, Box 33, Dvd 305.0226_a)
  - Rich Reel, undated; ID: 305.0227 (Box 12, Media ID: 305.0227, Box 33, Dvd 305.0227_a)
    Duration: 45 minutes
  - 1. Decade of Decadence 2. Elvis Costello Animation 3. David Johansen, undated; ID: 305.0228 (Box 12, Media ID: 305.0228, Box 33, Dvd 305.0228_a)
    Duration: 44 minutes
  - Surf, undated; ID: 305.0229 (Box 13, Media ID: 305.0229, Box 33, Dvd 305.0229_a)
  - Nutty Stuff, undated; ID: 305.0230 (Box 13, Media ID: 305.0230, Box 33, Dvd 305.0230_a)
    Duration: 00:38:55
  - Japanese Sci-fi and Music Videos, undated; ID: 305.0231 (Box 13, Media ID: 305.0231, Box 33, Dvd 305.0231_a)
    Duration: 58 minutes
  - Movie Stuff, undated; ID: 305.0232 (Box 13, Media ID: 305.0232, Box 33, Dvd 305.0232_a)
  - Funny Stuff, undated; ID: 305.0233 (Box 13, Media ID: 305.0233, Box 33, Dvd 305.0233_a)
  - Rockamerica, October 1980; ID: 305.0234 (Box 13, Media ID: 305.0234, Box 33, Dvd 305.0234_a)
  - Home Entertainment #4, undated; ID: 305.0235 (Box 13, Media ID: 305.0235, Box 33, Dvd 305.0235_a)
    Duration: 1 hour 2 minutes
  - 1. Elvis Presley and Milton Bearl 2. Jane Mansfield, Mickey Rooney and Ronald Reagan 3."Rock Around the Clock" Trailer, undated; ID: 305.0236 (Box 10, Media ID: 305.0236, Box 33, Dvd 305.0236_a)
  - Home Entertainment #2, undated; ID: 305.0237 (Box 13, Media ID: 305.0237, Box 33, Dvd 305.0237_a)
  - Factory Records Music Videos, undated; ID: 305.0238 (Box 13, Media ID: 305.0238, Box Shared Fales 134, Dvd 305.0238_a)
    Duration: 38 minutes
  - 1. Altered States 2. Superman Opening 3. Krypton Blows Up, etc., undated; ID: 305.0239 (Box 13, Media ID: 305.0239, Box Shared Fales 134, Dvd 305.0239_a)
  - 1. "Debs Behind Bars" 2. Time Lapse Photography 3. Devo, etc., undated; ID: 305.0240 (Box 13, Media ID: 305.0240, Box Shared Fales 134, Dvd 305.0240_a)
  - 1. "Ave Maria" 2.Change of Habit Trailer 3. Japanese Riot Squad Infomercial, etc., undated; ID: 305.0241 (Box 13, Media ID: 305.0241, Box Shared Fales 134, Dvd 05.0241_a)
  - 1. Show Lumania 2. Shox Lumania 3. Island of Dr. Moreau, etc., undated; ID: 305.0242 (Box 13, Media ID: 305.0242, Box Shared Fales 134, Dvd 305.0242_a)
  - 1. Eel + Octopus 2. Hindenberg 3. Keith Haring, etc., undated; ID: 305.0243 (Box 13, Media ID: 305.0243, Box Shared Fales 134, Dvd 305.0246_a)
  - 1. Stones (old) 2. Public Image 3. Devo, etc., undated; ID: 305.0244 (Box 13, Media ID: 305.0244, Box Shared Fales 134, Dvd 305.0244_a)
- Series VI: Nightclubbing
  The sixteen videos in Series VI contain episodes of the NIGHTCLUBBING television series that was broadcast as a local television show in New York City and was also screened at late night viewings at the Anthology Film Archives. While the majority of these recordings are undated, the dated videos were made during 1975-1980.
  - Dead Boys, 1977; ID: 305.0167 (Box 10, Media ID: 305.0167, Box 32, Dvd 305.0167_a)
  - Dead Boys, 1977 - 1979; ID: 305.0160 (Box 9, Media ID: 305.0160, Box 31, Dvd 305.0160_a)
  - Cramps, DNA, undated; ID: 305.0169 (Box 10, Media ID: 305.0169, Box 32, Dvd 305.0169_a)
    Black & White/Color, Sound
  - Hardcore 2, undated; ID: 305.0165 (Box 10, Media ID: 305.0165, Box 32, Dvd 305.0165_a)
  - Rock/Racism - CP, October 3, 1979; ID: 305.0156 (Box 9, Media ID: 305.0156, Box 31, Dvd 305.0156_a)
  - Kid Creaole & the Coconuts, undated; ID: 305.0159 (Box 9, Media ID: 305.0159, Box 31, Dvd 305.0159_a)
  - "Live Girls": Stilettos, Erasers, Desire, undated; ID: 305.0162 (Box 10, Media ID: 305.0162, Box 32, Dvd 305.0162_a)
  - Nuggets; Heartbreakers, undated; ID: 305.0158 (Box 9, Media ID: 305.0158, Box 32, Dvd 305.0158_a)
  - Raybeats Swimming Pool Ques, undated; ID: 305.0154 (Box 9, Media ID: 305.0154, Box 32, Dvd 305.0154_a)
  - "Real Rockers": Casualties; Heartbreakers, undated; ID: 305.0161 (Box 9, Media ID: 305.0161, Box 32, Dvd 305.0161_a)
    Duration: 46 minutes
  - Revelons, Only Ones at CBGB, undated; ID: 305.0168 (Box 10, Media ID: 305.0168, Box 32, Dvd 305.0168_a)
  - Roots of Hardcore; Hardcore Sampler: Dead Kennedys, Dead Boys, Heartbreakers, undated; ID: 305.0166 (Box 10, Media ID: 305.0166, Box 32, Dvd 305.0166_a)
  - Student Teachers; Pinups, undated; ID: 305.0157 (Box 9, Media ID: 305.0157, Box 31, Dvd 305.0157_a)
  - West Coast Offs, Dils, Dead Kennedys, undated; ID: 305.0164 (Box 10, Media ID: 305.0164, Box 32, Dvd 305.0164_a)
  - West Coast; More Live Girls, undated; ID: 305.0155 (Box 9, Media ID: 305.0155, Box 31, Dvd 305.0155_a)
  - History of the Heartbreakers, 1975 - 1980; ID: 305.0163 (Box 10, Media ID: 305.0163, Box 32, Dvd 305.0163_a)
- Series VIII: Logs
  - Logs, 1975-80, undated (Binder A)
    Contains tape logs, copies, and playbills of performances dating between 1975 and 1980.
  - Logs, 1975-80, undated (Binder B)
- Series IX: Press Clippings
  - Press Clippings, 1979-1982 (Binder C)
    Newspaper articles, advertisements, and press releases from 1979-1982.
  - Press Clippings, 2000-2012 (Binder D)
    Newspaper and magazine clippings, advertisements, and press releases, both US and international, dating from 2000-2012.